Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 2. Legislative Files, 1965-2011 TJU.2010.01.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 2. Legislative Files
1965-2011
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Specter, Arlen
TJU.2010.01.02
533.79 Linear Feet
The Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 2. Legislative Files document the legislative activities of Senator Specter and his office during his 30-year Congressional tenure from 1981 through 2011. The collection contains correspondence, reports, memos, research files, briefing books, hearing transcripts, publications, voting records, Congressional Records, and more.
Custodial History
Material was transferred to the care of Philadelphia University in 2010-2011 from the Federal Records Storage Facility in Suitland, Maryland, as well as the Senator's Washington, D.C. and Pennsylvania offices. The physical material was transferred to the University of Pittsburgh in 2014, with the exception of selected photographic and memorabilia items that remain at the Arlen Specter Center's Roxboro House for display. In 2016, Philadelphia University merged with Thomas Jefferson University, and is now known as Thomas Jefferson University- East Falls campus.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Arlen Specter to Philadelphia University in 2010. Philadelphia University and the University of Pittsburgh entered into a partnership to jointly manage the collection in 2013.
Biography
Born in Wichita, Kansas, on February 12, 1930, Arlen Specter came to Pennsylvania to attend the University of Pennsylvania. He married Joan Levy in 1953, and graduated from Yale Law School in 1956. He became assistant district attorney in Philadelphia in 1959. In 1962, Specter was recommended to serve on the Warren Commission, assembled to investigate the assassination of President John F. Kennedy. As part of the Commission, he was responsible for co-authoring the proposal of the "single bullet theory," determining that one bullet struck both President Kennedy and Texas Governor John Connally. Specter ran for Philadelphia district attorney in 1965, switching his Party membership to Republican in order to unseat the incumbent Democrat. He was successful, and served as district attorney from 1966 to 1974.
After an initial failed run for Senator and then for Governor of Pennsylvania, Specter was elected to the U.S. Senate in 1980. He would stay in this position from 1981 to 2011, making him the longest-tenured senator in Pennsylvania's history. During this time, he was a member of a number of Committees: Judiciary (1981-2011; Chair, 2007-2007), Appropriations (1981-2011), Veterans Affairs (1981-2011; Chair, 1997-2001 and 2003-2005), Select Intelligence (1985-1991; 1995-1997; Chair, 1995-1997), Special Aging (1991-1995; 2007-2011), Governmental Affairs (1997-2001; 2003-2005), and Environment and Public Works (2001-2003; 2009-2011).
Though elected as a Republican, Specter was a moderate on many issues, including healthcare reform, immigration, and abortion. He would often cross party lines, such as in voting against the confirmation of President Ronald Reagan's nominee Judge Robert Bork to the Supreme Court in 1987. Specter would again come into the spotlight during a Supreme Court nomination process in 1991, for his cross-examination of Professor Anita Hill regarding her allegations against nominee Clarence Thomas. In 1999, he would vote against the charges brought against President Bill Clinton, giving an answer of "not proven" to reflect his belief that Clinton had not received a fair trial.
As Senator, Specter championed a number of causes and influenced many legislative areas. He was frequently a member of Congressional Delegation trips, particularly to the Middle East, where he would speak out on the cause of freedom from religious persecution and the importance of strong diplomatic relations. He was also a proponent of funding for medical research, including the use of stem cells. He advocated for strict crime laws, particularly for career criminals. His focus on benefitting Pennsylvania could be seen through the pursuit of grant funding opportunities and his attempt to prevent the closure of the Philadelphia Naval Shipyard in the 1990s.
With the worsening of Congressional partisanship in the late 2000s, Specter found himself frequently voting with his Democratic peers. After being one of only three handful of Republicans to vote for the American Recovery and Reinvestment Act in 2009, Specter found himself increasingly marginalized within his party. In April 2009, he returned to the Democratic Party, helping to ensure the passage of the Affordable Care Act. Seeking re-election in 2010, he was defeated in the Democratic primary by Joe Sestak.
Specter's 30-year tenure in the Senate concluded in January 2011. After leaving the Senate, he partnered with Philadelphia University (now Jefferson-East Falls) to establish the Arlen Specter Center for Public Service. In the fall of 2012, Specter, who had previously beaten Hodgkin's lymphoma in 2005 while serving as Chair of the Judiciary Committee, was diagnosed with cancer. He died on October 14, 2012, aged 82.
Scope and Content Notes
The Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 2. Legislative Files comprises 488 boxes of material documenting the legislative activities of Senator Specter and his office during his 30-year Congressional tenure from 1981 through 2011. Included in this section are files related to work on specific committees, research files on areas of interest to the senator, files from legislative assistants employed in his office, and material on various other legislative activities. The collection contains correspondence, reports, memos, research files, briefing books, hearing transcripts, publications, voting records, Congressional Records, and more.
Arrangement
Group 2 is arranged into four series reflecting various aspects of the legislative work performed in Senator Specter's office:
Series I. Committee Files, 1965-2010
Series II. Research Files, 1967-2010
Series III. Legislative Assistant Files, 1965-2011
Series IV. Activities, 1981-2009
Related Material
Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 1. Pre-Senatorial Career Files, 1953-1980, TJU.2010.01.01
Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 3. Personal, Political and Official Files, 1944-2010, TJU.2010.01.03
Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 4. Office Administration Files, 1962-2010, TJU.2010.01.04
Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 5. Constituent Services Files, 1976-2007, TJU.2010.01.05
Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 6. Public Relations and Media Files, 1972-2010, TJU.2010.01.06
Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 7. Campaign Files, 1976-2004, TJU.2010.01.07
Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 8. Awards and Memorabilia, 1957-2010, TJU.2010.01.08
Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 9. Photographs, 1930-2010, TJU.2010.01.09
Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 10. Electronic Records, 1980-2010, TJU.2010.01.10
Impeachment; Agriculture -- Pennsylvania; Politicians; Legislators; Legislation -- Pennsylvania; International relations; Health care reform; Pennsylvania; Pennsylvania -- Politics and government; Government; United States. Congress. Senate; Specter, Arlen; United States. Department of Veterans Affairs; United States. Supreme Court; Roberts, John; Hill, Anita (Anita Louise); Bork, R. H. (Robert Heron); Clarence, Thomas; United States. Congress; Clinton, Bill
- Committee-Related Files, 1965-2010; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  Committee-Related Files contain research and preparatory material related to four Senate committees on which Senator Specter served or was interested in.
  - Appropriations Committee, 1981-2009; 1.
    Senator Specter served on the Appropriations Committee for his entire Senate tenure, from 1981 to 2011. During this time, he served on a number of subcommittees: Agriculture, Rural Development, and Related Agencies (1981-2011); Commerce, Justice, State and Judiciary and Related Agencies (1983-1987); Defense (1989-2011); District of Columbia (1981-1983, 1985-1987 (chair)); Energy and Water Development (1987-1993); Foreign Operations (1981-2011); Housing and Urban Development and Related Agencies (1981-1983, 2005-2011); Labor, Health and Human Services, Education and Related Agencies (1981-2001, 2003-2011 (chair 1995-2001, 2003-2007)); Military Construction (1987-1989); Transportation (1993-1999, 2001-2011); and Treasury and General Government (2003-2007).
    - General Committee Files, 1981-2009; 1.
      - Appropriations, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 2-4)
      - Appropriations, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 5-8)
      - Appropriations, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 9-11)
      - Appropriations, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Appropriations, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 13-18)
      - Appropriations, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
      - Appropriations, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Appropriations, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 4-5)
      - Appropriations, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Appropriations, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Appropriations, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Appropriations, Baltic states, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Appropriations, Budget Resolution, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Appropriations, Budget Resolution, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Appropriations, Budget Resolution, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Appropriations, Budget Resolution, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Appropriations, Budget Resolution, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Appropriations, Community Restoration Works, Operation Outward Reach, 2006-2008 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Appropriations, Corps of Engineers (COE), 2006 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Appropriations, COE, Budget, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Appropriations, COE, Language, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Appropriations, COE, Operations and Maintenance, A-76 competitive sourcing, Locks and dams, 2002-2007 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Appropriations, COE, Operations and Maintenance, Form, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Appropriations, Department of Labor Welfare to Work Competitive Grants, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Appropriations, Erie, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Appropriations, Harrisburg, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - Appropriations, The Hispanic Center, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - Appropriations, The Hispanic Center, Strategic plan, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - Appropriations, Legislative Activity in Education, 1981-1998 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - Appropriations, Edward Madigan nomination, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - Appropriations, Lynn Martin nomination, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - Appropriations, Bob Martinez nomination, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 29)
      - Appropriations, Omnibus appropriations, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - Appropriations, Omnibus highlights, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 31)
      - Appropriations, Omnibus tables, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 32)
      - Appropriations, Pain Relief Promotion Act, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations, Pennsylvania, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Appropriations, Philadelphia, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Appropriations, Pittsburgh, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Appropriations, Priority letters, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Appropriations, Requests, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 6-7)
      - Appropriations, Requests, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 8-11)
      - Appropriations, Requests, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 12-14)
      - Appropriations, Rescissions, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Appropriations, Rescissions, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Appropriations, Scranton, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Appropriations, S. 3, Senate Election Ethics Act, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Appropriations, S. 100, Central American Democracy and Development Act, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations, S. 173, Telecommunications Equipment Research and Manufacturing Competition Act, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Appropriations, S. 250, National Voter Registration Act, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Appropriations, S. 429, Consumer Protection Against Price-Fixing Act, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Appropriations, S. 1241, Comprehensive Violent Crime Control Act, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Appropriations, S. 1554, Unemployment Compensation, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Appropriations, S. J. 22, Gramm-Rudman-Hollings Waiver, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Appropriations, S. Res. 62, Biennial Committee Funding, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Appropriations, S. Res. 78, Resolution to Disapprove Fast Track Procedures, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Appropriations, S. Res. 117, Relative to Soviet Agriculture Export Credit Guarantees, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Appropriations, The Sierra Group, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Appropriations, Specter letters and chronological file, 1996-1998 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Appropriations, Supplemental appropriations, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Appropriations, Supplemental appropriations, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 14-16)
      - Appropriations, Supplemental appropriations, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 17-18)
      - Appropriations, Supplemental appropriations for aid to Kurdish refugees, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Appropriations, Supplemental appropriations and rescissions, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 20-23)
      - Appropriations, Taxpayer Refund Act, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - Appropriations, Taxpayer Refund Act, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations, Tobacco legislation, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Appropriations, VIP mail, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
      - Appropriations, Welfare reform issues, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Subcommittee on Agriculture, Rural Development and Related Agencies, 1981-2009; 2.
      - Appropriations, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Appropriations, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 7-12)
      - Appropriations, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 13-14)
      - Appropriations, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 15-17)
      - Appropriations, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
      - Appropriations, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 3-7)
      - Appropriations, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 8-9)
      - Appropriations, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 10-13)
      - Appropriations, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 1-5)
      - Appropriations, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 6-7)
      - Appropriations, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 8-11)
      - Appropriations, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 12-13)
      - Appropriations, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 1-7)
      - Appropriations, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Appropriations, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Appropriations, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Appropriations, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 11-13)
      - Appropriations, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 14-16)
      - Appropriations, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 1-5)
      - Appropriations, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 6-10)
      - Appropriations, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Appropriations, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - H.R. 2698, Agriculture appropriations, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - US Department of Agriculture (USDA) Budget Explanatory Notes Volume 1, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 14-17)
      - USDA Budget Explanatory Notes Volume 2, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
      - USDA Budget Explanatory Notes Volume 1, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 5-8)
      - USDA Budget Explanatory Notes Volume 2, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 9-11)
    - Subcommittee on Commerce, State, Justice and Judiciary, 1984-2001; 3.
      - Appropriations, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Appropriations, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 13-17)
      - Appropriations, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - Appropriations, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 2-3)
      - Appropriations, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 4-15)
      - Appropriations, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 16-17)
      - Appropriations, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 1-4)
      - Appropriations, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 5-6)
      - Appropriations, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - H.R. 2608, Commerce, Justice, State, the Judiciary and Related Agencies, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Subcommittee on Defense, 1981-2001; 4.
      - Appropriations, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Appropriations, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 10-11)
      - Appropriations, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 12-14)
      - Appropriations, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 15-16)
      - Appropriations, 1990-1993 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Appropriations, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Appropriations, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
      - Appropriations, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 3-5)
      - Appropriations, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Appropriations bill, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Appropriations bill, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Appropriations bill, Amendments, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Appropriations bill, Conference, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Appropriations bill, Conferences and wish lists, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 11-14)
      - Appropriations bill, Conferences and wish lists, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 15-17)
      - Appropriations bill, Proposals, 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Appropriations bill, Proposals, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations bill, Senate actions, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Briefing charts, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Budget, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Budget, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 5-6)
      - Budget floor statements, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 7-8)
      - Budget items, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Budget project, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Budget rescissions, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 11-12)
      - H.R. 3116 amendments, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Letters, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Local concerns, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Memos, Copies, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Military construction appropriations, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Military construction appropriations bill, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Military construction bills and reports, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Military construction program, 1983-1985 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Military construction wish list, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1995-2000 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Subcommittee on District of Columbia, 1981-2001; 5.
      - Appropriations, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - Appropriations, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - Appropriations, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - Appropriations, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - Appropriations, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - Appropriations, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - Appropriations, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - H.R. 2699, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Subcommittee on Energy and Water, 1981-2006; 6.
      - Appropriations, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 2-6)
      - Appropriations, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 7-12)
      - Appropriations, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 13-14)
      - Appropriations, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
      - Appropriations, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 3-7)
      - Appropriations, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 8-10)
      - Appropriations, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Appropriations, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 12-14)
      - Appropriations, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Appropriations, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Appropriations, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Alternative fuels, 1994-1996 (Box 22, Folder 5-6)
      - Coal issues, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Environment and Public Works Committee appropriations and amendments, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 8-10)
      - Environment and Public Works Committee, Private property rights bill, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 11-12)
      - H.R. 2427, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Lehigh Valley, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Superfund Recycling Equity Act, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 15-16)
      - Waste Technologies Industries, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Subcommittee on Foreign Operations, 1981-2002; 7.
      - Appropriations, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Appropriations, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - Appropriations, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Appropriations, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 1-6)
      - Appropriations, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 7-8)
      - Appropriations, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Appropriations, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Appropriations, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Appropriations bill, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Appropriations bill, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Appropriations wish lists, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Continuing appropriations, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Export financing appropriations, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Foreign assistance appropriations, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Foreign operations bill markup, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Security assistance hearing, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - S. 1367, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - S. 1433, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - S. 1435, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - S. 1435, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Supplemental appropriations, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Subcommittee on the Interior, 1990-2001; 8.
      - Appropriations, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 3-8)
      - Appropriations, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 9-10)
      - Appropriations, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 11-13)
      - Appropriations, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 14-15)
      - Appropriations, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
      - Appropriations, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 3-5)
      - Appropriations, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 6-8)
      - Appropriations, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 9-15)
      - Appropriations, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 1-6)
      - Appropriations, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Appropriations, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Appropriations, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 9-11)
      - New Urban Agenda, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 12-13)
      - Pennsylvania projects, 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 14-15)
      - Pennsylvania projects, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
    - Subcommittee on Labor, Health and Human Services, Education and Related Agencies, 1981-2009; 9.
      - Appropriations, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Appropriations, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 4-15)
      - Appropriations, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
      - Appropriations, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Appropriations, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 4-5)
      - Appropriations, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Appropriations, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Appropriations, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Appropriations, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 9-14)
      - Appropriations, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 15-17)
      - Appropriations, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 2-10)
      - Appropriations, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 11-17)
      - Appropriations, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 2-11)
      - Appropriations, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 12-13)
      - Appropriations, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 1-6)
      - Appropriations, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 7-13)
      - Appropriations, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 1-8)
      - Appropriations, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 9-12)
      - Appropriations, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 13-15)
      - Appropriations, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 1-3)
      - Appropriations, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Appropriations, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 5-8)
      - Appropriations charts, undated (Box 33, Folder 9-10)
      - Campus Crime Disclosure Act, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 11-12)
      - Department of Labor requests, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Department of Labor requests, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Fiscal year 2005 charts, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Fiscal year 2006 charts, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - General, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Lehigh University, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - Mount Aloysius College, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) requests, 2004 (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - NASA requests, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 21)
      - S. 323, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Subcommittee on Legislative Activities, 1991-2002; 10.
      - Appropriations, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 23)
      - Appropriations, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 24-26)
      - Appropriations, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 27)